

Krasneho 1341/67, Brno, Czech Republic

□ (+420) 732 772 904 | ☑ jirka.kopecky@outlook.com | ☑ jirikopecky | 🛅 jiri-kopecky



Summary_

Software developer at Honeywell. 5+ years experience developing server and cloud solutions for connected devices. Nerd who love learn about new tools and services, mainly from the .NET world. Out of work loves to play computer games and to read good Sci-Fi or Fantasy book.

Work Experience

Honeywell - HTS CZ

SOFTWARE DESIGN ENGINEER

- Participated on architecture of several IoT Cloud solutions
- Implemented several microservices in C# targeting Microsoft Service Fabric
- · Implemented CI/CD pipeline using PowerShell scripts, Atlassian Bamboo and Octopus deployment server
- · Deployed a centralized logging environment (ElasticSearch, Kibana) which gather log data from microservices.

Honeywell - HTS CZ

TECHNICAL SUPPORT / INTERNSHIP

Support of engineering team that developed IoT services

Blue Pixel Solutions a.s.

C# DEVELOPER / INTERNSHIP

• Development of desktop and web applications in C#

Brno, Czech Republic

May 2013 - PRESENT

Brno, Czech Republic

Apr. 2012 - Apr. 2013

Brno, Czech Republic

Aug. 2008 - Apr. 2010

Presentation

Microsoft Build 2018 Seattle, WA

PRESENTER FOR <HOW HONEYWELL MIGRATED THEIR SMART THERMOSTAT APPLICATION TO SERVICE FABRIC>

May 2018

- Summarized how Honeywell Homes Cloud team migrated their solution from Azure Cloud Services to Microsoft Service Fabric
- Available on YouTube: https://youtu.be/VTH2XnMSZ2o

ŽijemelT Brno, Czech Republic

PRESENTER FOR < DEPLOYMENT AUTOMATION IN AZURE>

Feb. 2018

- Small Czech conference intended for students, held at Faculty of Information Technology, Brno University of Technology
- Introduced different ways how to automate code deployment to Microsoft Azure

Education

Brno University of Technology, Faculty of Information Technology

Brno, Czech Republic

Sep. 2008 - Jun. 2012

Certifications

MICROSOFT EXAMS

• 532: Developing Microsoft Azure Solutions

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

483: Programming in C#

Skills

Programming C#, .NET, .NET Core, PowerShell, TypeScript, JavaScript

Cloud Service Fabric, Docker, Microsoft Azure (IoT Hub, Event Hubs, Azure Active Directory)

Web React, Redux, HTML5, CSS

Languages Czech, English

JIRI KOPECKY · RÉSUMÉ

JUNE 28, 2018